open chrome and type
online.moneylife.com.ph
slash login then sign in with your email
address and password
if you don't have account yet you can
register just click the option to
register
and then tap sign in
and you have an option here where you
can receive the
one-time password you can choose either
email ad or your registered
mobile number
and then check one-time password sent to
your email or
by text
and then enter the one-time password and
tap
proceed
and now here you can see your overview
payment
and the date and if you want to pay
online
just tap the three lines
on top right corner then
payment
tap payment and then make a
payment and here will be the details for
your payment
and so far my policies have been paid